{
  "task": [
    {
      "question": " Why did the herdsmen of Lot and Abraham quarrel?",
      "time": "12000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": "a. The herdsmen of Lot were stealing sheep "
        },
        {
          "choice": "b. Their herds were getting mixed "
        },
        {
          "choice": "c. The land could not support both of them "
        },
        {
          "choice": "d. Abram was sacrificing Lot's sheep "
        }
      ],
      "answer": "c. The land could not support both of them ",
      "type": "epi_9"
    },
    {
      "question": " After Lot left Abraham, what did God promise Abraham? ",
      "time": "10000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": "a.  A descendent who would rule "
        },
        {
          "choice": "b. All the land he could see "
        },
        {
          "choice": "c. A son born of Sarah "
        },
        {
          "choice": "d. Herds beyond counting "
        }
      ],
      "answer": "b. All the land he could see ",
      "type": "epi_9"
    },
    {
      "question": " After leaving Egypt, Abraham went to what region of Canaan? ",
      "time": "10000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": "a. Negev "
        },
        {
          "choice": "b. Hill country "
        },
        {
          "choice": "c.  Philistine plain "
        },
        {
          "choice": "d.  Galilee "
        }
      ],
      "answer": "a. Negev ",
      "type": "epi_9"
    },
    {
      "question": " How did Abraham solve the problem of the quarrel between the herdsmen of Lot?  ",
      "time": "15000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": " a. Lot would return to Haran with his herds "
        },
        {
          "choice": " b. Melchisedek would be sought out to solve the problem "
        },
        {
          "choice": " c.  All herds would be split evenly "
        },
        {
          "choice": " d. They would part company "
        }
      ],
      "answer": " d. They would part company ",
      "type": "epi_9"
    },
    {
      "question": "The sin of the men of Sodom was against whom ?",
      "time": "8000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": "a. Lot "
        },
        {
          "choice": "b. Their neighbors "
        },
        {
          "choice": "c. The Lord "
        },
        {
          "choice": "d. Themselves "
        }
      ],
      "answer": "c. The Lord ",
      "type": "epi_9"
    },
    {
      "question": "Abraham became wealthy in all of the following commodities EXCEPT?  ",
      "time": "8000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": "a. Silver "
        },
        {
          "choice": "b.  Livestock "
        },
        {
          "choice": "c.  Gold "
        },
        {
          "choice": "d.  Jewels "
        }
      ],
      "answer": "d.  Jewels ",
      "type": "epi_9"
    },
    {
      "question": " Why did Lot desire the plain of Jordan?",
      "time": "10000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": "a. It had much pasture "
        },
        {
          "choice": "b. It was warm "
        },
        {
          "choice": "c. It was a center for trading "
        },
        {
          "choice": "d. It was well watered "
        }
      ],
      "answer": "d. It was well watered ",
      "type": "epi_9"
    },
    {
      "question": " When Abraham returned to the site between Bethel and Ai where he had built an altar, what did he do as he had done before?",
      "time": "15000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": "a. He gave God a tenth of everything God had blessed him with "
        },
        {
          "choice": "b.  He circumcised Lot "
        },
        {
          "choice": "c.  He called on the name of the Lord "
        },
        {
          "choice": "d.  He sacrificed his son "
        }
      ],
      "answer": "c.  He called on the name of the Lord ",
      "type": "epi_9"
    },
    {
      "question": " Who is the sons of Abraham? ",
      "time": "8000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": " a. Ishmael & Isaac"
        },
        {
          "choice": " b. Jacob & Esau"
        },
        {
          "choice": " c. Nimrod & Judah"
        },
        {
          "choice": " d. Simeon & Manaseh"
        }
      ],
      "answer": " a. Ishmael & Isaac",
      "type": "epi_9"
    },
    {
      "question": " After Lot left Abram, Abram settled by the great trees of Mamre which are by what town? ",
      "time": "8000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": "a.  Beersheba "
        },
        {
          "choice": "b.  Jerusalem "
        },
        {
          "choice": "c.  Hebron "
        },
        {
          "choice": "d.  Bethlehem "
        }
      ],
      "answer": "c.  Hebron ",
      "type": "epi_9"
    }
  ]
}






